The store will not work correctly in the case when cookies are disabled.

**JavaScript seems to be disabled in your browser.** For the best experience on our site, be sure to turn on Javascript in your browser.

[Cyber Monday Sale **Up to 50% off** Order now, sale ends soon!

* 00
    
    Hours
    
* :
* 00
    
    Minutes
    
* :
* 00
    
    Seconds](https://www.womanizer.com/eu/sale)

[Cyber Monday Sale**Up to 50% off**

Order now! Sale ends in

* 00
    
    Hours
    
* :
* 00
    
    Minutes
    
* :
* 00
    
    Seconds](https://www.womanizer.com/eu/sale)

    * [NEW
        
        Liberty 2 Iggy Azalea](https://www.womanizer.com/eu/iggy-azalea)
    * [NEW
        
        Vibe](https://www.womanizer.com/eu/vibe)
    * [NEW
        
        24 Days of Pleasure](https://www.womanizer.com/eu/couples-advent-calendar)
    * [NEW
        
        24 Days of Pleasure](https://www.womanizer.com/eu/24-days-of-pleasure-premium-advent-calendar)
    * [NEW
        
        Blend](https://www.womanizer.com/eu/blend)

    * [NEW
        
        24 Days of Pleasure](https://www.womanizer.com/eu/couples-advent-calendar)
    * [NEW
        
        24 Days of Pleasure](https://www.womanizer.com/eu/24-days-of-pleasure-premium-advent-calendar)
    * [NEW
        
        Blend](https://www.womanizer.com/eu/blend)

Go

Search

European Union English

Shipping destination

Language

Update Preferences

* Privacy Policy

**Data Protection Policy**
==========================

This website is operated by WOW Tech Europe GmbH (“WOW” "we" or "us “). For further details please see our [imprint](https://wowtech.com/privacy-policy/).

With this Data Protection Policy we inform you about how we use your personal data when you visit our website and when we provide our services and your rights in this respect.

### **Processing of Data**

#### **1\. Visiting our website**

Each time you visit our website your browser automatically transmits information to us. Such as IP-address of your device, date and time of access, name and address of the requested file, transmitted amount of data, notification as to whether the request was successful, information on the browser and operating system used, name of your internet provider. This data is processed and temporally stored technically facilitate the use of the website (connection setup). In addition, the data is evaluated in anonymous and aggregated form (i.e. drawing conclusions about individual users won't be possible), statistically in the interest of system security, the technical administration of the network infrastructure and to optimize our website. These are all our legitimate interests, so we base the processing on Art. 6 para. 1 f) of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

#### **2\. Legal Basis for the Processing of Personal Data**

We use our website as an informational platform to answer your enquiries. To make contact requests more personal, you have the option of providing about you, comments and questions via a contact form. The respective legal basis for such processing is our legitimate interest (Art. 6 para. 1 f) GDPR).

We may process your personal data for the purpose of preparing offers and fulfilling contractual obligations (based on Art. 6 para. 1 b) GDPR).

To the extent we process your personal data for accounting, cost accounting and complying with legal obligations (e.g. commercial and tax law), we base this processing on Art. 6 para. 1 c) GDPR.

On the legal basis of Art. 6 para. 1 f) GDPR we collect information through, among other things, participation in conferences and events, personal recommendations and employee registration by employers for the use of our services and by selected external business partners.

Based on your consent (Art. 6 para. 1 a) GDPR) we will use your data to send you information about products, services, events and other information worth knowing about our company. You can revoke your consent at any time with effect for the future under the contact information provided within the [imprint](https://wowtech.com/privacy-policy/).

#### **3\. User account**

You have the possibility to register a user account on our website. We have marked the data that are mandatory for registration within the form as obligatory fields. This information is required for setting up a user account and is processed on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 b) GDPR. Any other information you provide to us that goes beyond the mandatory information will be processed by us on the basis of our legitimate interest in using your voluntarily provided information for the user account (Art. 6 para. 1 f) GDPR). If you wish to object to data processing with regard to your voluntarily provided information, please contact the e-mail address given in the [imprint](https://wowtech.com/privacy-policy/).

#### **4\. Ordering process**

If you order an article on our website, we need personal data in order to fulfil our contractual obligations towards you. It is possible that you complete an order without registering a user account as well as that you use the information saved under your user account for a faster and more comfortable order. In both cases, details of the billing and shipping address as well as payment information are required for contract execution. The legal basis for the processing of the aforementioned data is Art. 6 para. 1 b) GDPR. On the basis of our legitimate interests (Art. 6 para. 1 f) GDPR), we process information which you provide to us that goes beyond what is necessary for the performance of the contract. If you wish to object to this data processing, please contact the e-mail address given in the [imprint](https://wowtech.com/privacy-policy/).

We offer various payment options in cooperation with service providers. If you decide to use a payment option, payment data will be transmitted to the individual service providers as part of the execution of transactions. In some cases, payment service providers reserve the right to carry out a credit assessment based on mathematical-statistical procedures involving the use of address data. Some payment service providers provide you with information on the credit agencies used, which you can view in the browser window in which the payment option is offered before completing payment. Among the payment service providers with whom we cooperate are the following companies, whose Data Protection Policies can also be accessed via the following links:

* Amazon Pay: Amazon Payments Europe s.c.a., 5, Rue Plaetis, L 2338 Luxembourg - [https://pay.amazon.de/help/201751600](https://pay.amazon.de/help/201751600)
* PayPal: PayPal (Europe) S.a.r.l. et Cie, S.C.A, 22-24 Boulevard Royal, L-2449 Luxembourg - [https://www.paypal.com/de/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full?locale.x=en\_DE#rAnnex](https://www.paypal.com/de/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full?locale.x=en_DE#rAnnex)
* Visa: Visa Europe Management Services Limited, Neue Mainzer Strasse 66-68, 60311 Frankfurt am Main Germany - [https://www.visa.de/nutzungsbedingungen/visa-privacy-center.html](https://www.visa.de/nutzungsbedingungen/visa-privacy-center.html)
* Mastercard: Mastercard Europe SA, Chaussée de Tervuren 198A, B-1410 Waterloo Belgium - [https://www.mastercard.de/de-de.html](https://www.mastercard.de/de-de.html)
* griopay: giropay GmbH, An der Welle 4, 60322 Frankfurt am Main Germany - [https://www.giropay.de/agb/index.html](https://www.giropay.de/agb/index.html)
* Payone: BS PAYONE GmbH, Lyoner Straße 9, D-60528 Frankfurt/Main, Deutschland – [https://www.payone.com/DE-de](https://www.payone.com/DE-de)

The legal basis for data processing is Art. 6 para. 1 b) GDPR and data processing which goes beyond what is necessary for the execution of the contract is carried out on the basis of our legitimate interests (Art. 6 para. 1 f) GDPR).

#### **5\. Warranty & RMA Request**

If you, as a buyer of one of our products, make a warranty claim, we will need your personal details as well as information about your purchase from us. You also have the option of submitting attachments to us using the corresponding form. We use the NetSuite service, which is operated by Oracle (ORACLE Deutschland B.V. & Co. KG, Riesstraße 25, D-80992 Munich), for the central recording of enquiries and for forwarding them to us. The data marked as mandatory fields are necessary for checking and processing and, if necessary, for safeguarding your warranty claim and are processed on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 b) and c) GDPR. We process further information that you voluntarily provide to us on the basis of our legitimate interests in the use of this information (Art. 6 para. 1 f) GDPR). If you wish to object to data processing with regard to your voluntary details, please contact the e-mail address given in the [imprint](https://wowtech.com/privacy-policy/).

#### **6\. Write a feedback or comment**

It is possible that you send us your feedback on one of our products or a comment for any other reason. We process the information you provide in the forms in order to improve our offer and, if necessary, to be able to contact you on the basis of our legitimate interests (Art. 6 para. 1 f) GDPR). We use the NetSuite service, which is operated by Oracle (ORACLE Deutschland B.V. & Co. KG, Riesstraße 25, D-80992 Munich), for the central recording of enquiries and for forwarding them to us. If you want to object to the data processing afterwards, please contact us using the e-mail address in the [imprint](https://wowtech.com/privacy-policy/).

#### **7\. Business Partner contact form**

As a wholesaler you can send us an inquiry on our website. In order to better classify and process your enquiry, we ask you to fill in the relevant information in the form. We process the data entered in the form in order to handle your request. If the processing of the request directly concerns a future contractual relationship with you, the legal basis is Art. 6 para. 1 b) GDPR. In the case of other inquiries, we process the data on the basis of our legitimate interests in processing your inquiry (Art. 6 para. 1 f) GDPR). We use the NetSuite service, which is operated by Oracle (ORACLE Deutschland B.V. & Co. KG, Riesstraße 25, D-80992 Munich), for the central recording of enquiries and for forwarding them to us. In the last-mentioned case, you can object to data processing by sending an e-mail to the address given in the [imprint](https://wowtech.com/privacy-policy/).

#### **8\. Cookies, Pixel and similar technologies**

Cookies are small text files, pixel are small graphic files, that are stored on your computer (together hereinafter "Cookies"). Cookies make it possible to identify you as a specific customer and to store both your personal preferences when using our website and technical information. The main benefit for you is that you do not have to enter specific information stored in the Cookies every time you visit our website. Cookies do not necessarily reveal personal information. If, however, you enter personal information on our website, this may be associated with the data stored in the cookies.

**Unless otherwise expressly stated in the following, we base this processing on our legitimate interest in offering you a handy website Art. 6 (1) f) GDPR.**

You can deactivate or block the storage of Cookies in your browser generally or only for our site. To find out how, please see the help function of your browser. Please note that blocking Cookies may impair the user-friendliness of our website.

**Cookie consent:** In order to be able to tell if you consented to the processing of data in connection with Cookies, we implement a cookie which informs us if you have consented and to what kind of processing you gave your consent or not.

**Own cookies:** For some of our services it is necessary that we use our own cookies. The main purpose of our own cookies is to make the use of our services as time-saving as possible by, for example, saving the language you have selected. We use our own cookies in particular for login authentication, load distribution and to note that information placed on our website has been displayed to you.

#### **8.1 Google Analytics**

On our website we use Google Analytics a web analysis service of Google LLC. (1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA, "Google"). Google Analytics enables the generation of statistics to help us understand website traffic and its sources. We use Google Analytics solely for statistical purposes, such as to track how many users have clicked on a particular item or information. The retention period of the cookie is 2 years. The legal basis is legitimate interests (Art. 6 para. 1 f) GDPR). Google Analytics is based on cookies and records information about your use of our website including your IP address. To prevent users being identified by their IP addresses, we use a special code to ensure that your IP address is recorded solely in truncated and therefore anonymized form. It is no longer possible to identify individual users with this truncated IP address. Further information on data protection when using Google Analytics can be found under the following link. You can prevent the collection of data through the Google Analytics cookie by installing the plug-in available at the following link: tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

**General information on Google's processing**: The information recorded by Google is transmitted to Google based in the United States. Google has self-certified its adherence to the EU-US Privacy Shield, . Please click here for further information on data protection at Google:

You can change your settings by going to the Google Marketing Platform's deactivation page () or the deactivation page of the NAI (Network Advertising Initiative). Alternatively, you can deactivate Google Cookies on the Digital Advertising Alliance website using the following link (). You can also block the storing of Cookies by changing the settings in your browser.

#### **8.2 Google Analytics Audience**

We use Google Analytics Audiences, a service provided by Google. Google Analytics Audience uses cookies that are stored on your computer and other mobile devices (e.g. smartphones, tablets, etc.) to help analyze how users use these devices (legal basis is consent (Art. 6 (1) a) GDPR)). The retention period for the cookie is 2 years. Google gains access to the cookies created by Google AdWords and Google Analytics. In the course of use, data, such as the IP address and user activities, is transmitted to a server of Google. You can prevent Google from collecting the data as described under the ["General information on Google's processing"](https://www.womanizer.com/eu/privacy-policy#gi-gp) section above.

For further information on data protection when using Google Analytics and how to install the browser plugin to prevent Google Analytics from tracking your activities please see the ["Google Analytics"](https://www.womanizer.com/eu/privacy-policy#gi-gp) section (8.1) above.

#### **8.3 Google Tag Manager**

On our website we use the Google Tag Manager of Google, which is used to trigger tags that we manage through an interface. The Tag Manager tool itself (which implements the tags) works without the use of cookies and does not collect personal data. However, the tool triggers other tags that may collect personal data. Google Tag Manager does not access such data. If a deactivation has been made at domain or cookie level, it will remain in effect for all tracking tags implemented with Google Tag Manager.

For further information on the processing by Google and how to prevent Google from processing please see the ["General information on Google's processing (8.1.)"](https://www.womanizer.com/eu/privacy-policy#gi-gp) section above.

#### **8.4 Google AdWords / Google AdWords Conversion**

We use Google AdWords and Google AdWords Conversion of Google to measure the efficiency of individual ads, offers and functions. A cookie is placed as soon as you click on a Google ad. This cookie is not intended for personal identification but to enable us to ascertain whether you return to the website with the specific offer within the cookie's validity of 30 days. The information obtained by the conversion cookie is for compiling conversion statistics for AdWords customers who opted for conversion tracking. We gain information on the total number of users who clicked on an ad and were forwarded to a website with a conversion tracking tag.

Further information on Google's processing of data and how you can disable the respective processing under the ["General information on Google's processing (8.1.)"](https://www.womanizer.com/eu/privacy-policy#gi-gp) section above.

#### **8.5 DoubleClick**

DoubleClick is a service provided by Google. DoubleClick uses cookies to display advertisements that may be relevant to you. A pseudonymous identification number is assigned to your browser in order to check which ads were displayed to you and which ads were viewed. The use of DoubleClick cookies enables Google and its partner websites to display ads based on previous visits to our or other websites. The legal basis is consent (Art. 6 (1) a) GDPR). The information generated by the cookies is transferred to a Google server in the USA. Google only transfers the data to third parties on the basis of legal provisions or within the scope of order processing. Data processed with DoubleClick is stored for up to 2 years and cookies are deleted after 11 months. For further information on Google's processing of data and how you may prevent Google from doing so please see the ["General information on Google's processing (8.1.)"](https://www.womanizer.com/eu/privacy-policy#gi-gp) section above.

#### **8.6 Google Dynamic Remarketing**

Google Dynamic Remarketing is a service provided by Google. Our website uses a pixel which establishes a connection to Google servers. Information transmitted to Google for example includes that you have visited our website. Google associates this information with an ID that is stored on your device in the form of a cookie or is provided by your device. If you visit other websites also using Google Dynamic Remarketing, this information will be linked to your pseudonymous ID. The legal basis is consent (Art. 6 (1) a) GDPR). However, it is not clear to us which other websites you visit. We can also provide our websites with so-called "remarketing tags". This means that we include keywords in our website that contain statements about the content of the page displayed (such as product or service categories). The keywords we use do not contain any personally identifiable information. Google receives and stores these keywords for the above-mentioned recognition features. If you visit a page that we have identified with a specific product category, Google will store the respective keyword and associate it with your recognition characteristics. The processed data is stored for a period of two years. Further information on Google\`s processing and how you can prevent it can be found above in the ["General information on Google's processing (8.1.)"](https://www.womanizer.com/eu/privacy-policy#gi-gp) section.

#### **8.7 Digital Window (Awin affiliate marketing)**

For affiliate marketing we are members of the affiliate program of AWIN AG, Eichhornstraße 3, 10785 Berlin, Germany. AWIN uses cookies to trace the origin of the conclusion of the contract. Among other things, AWIN recognizes that you have clicked on the partner link provided and have subsequently entered into a contract. The legal basis is our legitimate interest. You can disable cookies from the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI). deactivation page or from the Digital Advertising Alliance website by using the following link. You can also prevent the storage of cookies using the general settings of your browser. Information on data processing by AWIN can be found at.

#### **8.8 Trusted Shops**

To display our Trusted Shops seal of approval and our collected reviews as well as to offer Trusted Shops products to buyers after an order, this website includes the Trusted Shops Trustbadge, an offer of Trusted Shops GmbH, Subbelrather Str. 15C, 50823 Cologne, Germany. When you call up the trust badge, the web server automatically saves a so-called server log file, which contains, for example, your IP address, the date and time of the call, the amount of data transferred and the requesting provider (access data) and documents the request. These access data are not evaluated and are automatically overwritten at the latest seven days after the end of your page visit. Legal basis are our legitimate interests. You can disable cookies from the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI). deactivation page or from the Digital Advertising Alliance website by using the following link. You can also prevent the storage of cookies by using the general configuration of your browser.

Further personal data will only be transferred to Trusted Shops if you decide to use Trusted Shops products after placing an order or if you have already registered for their use. In this case, the contractual agreement between you and Trusted Shops applies and the legal basis is Art. 6 para. 1 b) and f) GDPR.

#### **8\. 9 Threat Metrix**

In order to secure our orders and to protect ourselves against payment defaults, we check frequent fraud patterns and anomalies. For this purpose, order and payment data (e.g. address, article, payment method) and device information (e.g. device, browser) are processed. Within this scope we work with services ThreatMetrix, Inc. 160 W. Santa Clara St., Suite 1400, San Jose, California 95113, USA "Threat Metrix" together. Threat Metrix compares device data with a network of trusted identities to prevent abuse and crime. In the event that personal data is transferred to the United States, Threat Metrix is self-certified under the Privacy Shield. Data processing is based on our legitimate interest in protecting against misuse and securing orders. You can disable cookies from the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI). deactivation page or from the Digital Advertising Alliance website by using the following link. You can also prevent the storage of cookies by using the general configuration of your browser.

#### **8.10 Amazon Pay and PayPal Cookies**

To integrate Amazon Pay and the PayPal payment functions, cookies are used based on our legitimate interests. You can deactivate or delete cookies in your browser, but this will prevent the payment options from working.

#### **8.11 ADCELL**

On our website we use ADCELL, a German affiliate network for affiliate marketing, which is operated by Firstlead GmbH, Rosenfelder Str. 15-16, 10315 Berlin. Via ADCELL, registered providers can advertise their offers within the framework of programmes. After clicking on Affiliate Marketing Links, which lead to offers on external websites, a cookie is stored by ADCELL, which contains an ID, which allows an assignment for ADCELL. In this way, it is possible for ADCELL to recognize that you have become aware of the offer via our website and that you have called up the website. Even a possible purchase of the product can be traced and assigned to our affiliate ID. Cookies that we set with the help of ADCELL have a storage period of one year. The purpose of processing the data is to track the various successes (transaction, lead, sale) and to process commission payments. At you have the possibility to prevent data processing with the help of ADCELL. You can disable cookies from the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) . deactivation page or from the Digital Advertising Alliance website by using the following link. You can also prevent the storage of cookies via the general settings of your browser.

#### **8.12 Rakuten Advertising**

We partner with Rakuten Advertising, who may collect personal information when you interact with our site. The collection and use of this information is subject to the privacy policy located here: https://rakutenadvertising.com/legal-notices/services-privacy-policy/.

#### **9\. reCAPTCHA**

In order to protect your entries on our website, we use the re-CAPTCHA service of Google on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 f) DSGVO. The query is used to differentiate whether the entry is made by a human being or misused by automated, machine processing. This purpose also represents our legitimate interest. The query includes sending the IP address to Google for the service reCAPTCHA.

Further information on Google\`s processing can be found above in the ["General information on Google's processing"](https://www.womanizer.com/eu/privacy-policy#gi-gp) section 8.1.

#### **10\. Lotteries and surveys**

In order to participate in competitions, it is necessary to provide personal data. We use this data for the duration and for the implementation of the respective competition (incl. drawing of the winners, notification of the winners and possibly the losers, possibly publication of the names of the winners, sending the prize etc.). If the prizes are provided by someone other than WOW, we will send the winners' personal data to this prize sponsor or its service provider. Otherwise, all personal data of the participant will not be passed on to third parties without consent, nor will they be made available for use. The legal basis for the processing is Art. 6 (1) lit. b GDPR.

If you participate in one of our surveys, we use your data for market and opinion research. We evaluate the data anonymously for internal purposes. If surveys are exceptionally not evaluated anonymously, the data will only be collected with your consent. In the case of anonymous surveys, the GDPR is not applicable and in the case of exceptional personal evaluations, the legal basis is the aforementioned consent pursuant to Art. 6 para. 1 a) GDPR.

#### **11\. Newsletter**

When subscribing to our newsletter on our website we will process your data (e.g. name, e-mail address, IP address and date and time of your subscription). For the registration for our newsletter we use a double opt-in procedure: After your subscription you will receive an e-mail asking you to confirm your registration. This confirmation ensures is required so that no unauthorized third party can register with your e-mail address. The collection of personal data serves to send the newsletter. The legal basis is consent (Art. 6 (1) a) GDPR).

The data will be saved as long as the subscription to the newsletter is active. You can revoke your con-sent for example via the "unsubscribe" link in every newsletter or by sending an e-mail to the e-mail address in the [imprint](https://wowtech.com/privacy-policy/).

In our newsletters, we use common technologies which allow us to measure the interactions with the newsletters (e.g. opening of the e-mail, clicked links). We use this data in pseudonymous form for general statistical evaluations as well as for the optimization and further development of our content and customer communication. This is done with the help of small graphics embedded in the newsletter (so-called pixels). The data is collected exclusively under a pseudonym and is not linked to your other personal data. The legal basis for this is your consent (Art. 6 para. 1 a) GDPR). If you do not want us to analyze the effectiveness of our newsletter, you can deactivate graphics in your e-mail program by default or unsubscribe from the newsletter. The data relating to the interaction with our newsletters is stored pseudonymously for 30 days and then completely anonymized.

#### **12\. Press mailing list**

If you would like to be included in our press mailing list, you can register for it on our website. After registering, you will receive a confirmation e-mail with a link, after clicking on this link you have successfully registered for our press mailing list. We process the information you enter in the form in order to send you press related content and inquires on the basis of your consent (Art. 6 (1) a) DSGVO). To unsubscribe from the press mailing list and revoke your consent, please contact us under [press@womanizer.com](mailto:press@womanizer.com).

#### **13\. YouTube videos**

We use the provider You Tube to be able to present videos to you. YouTube is operated by YouTube LLC with its headquarters at 901 Cherry Avenue, San Bruno, CA 94066, USA. YouTube is represented by Google. The legal basis for the use of YouTube plug-ins is Article 6 para. 1 f) GDPR. 

We use embedded YouTube videos in advanced privacy mode. According to YouTube, this means the following: YouTube does not store cookies for a user who displays a website with an embedded YouTube video player but does not click on the video to start playback. When you click on the YouTube video player, YouTube may store cookies on the user's computer, but we do not store personal cookie information for embedded video playback.

For further information on the processing by please see the ["General information on Google's processing"](https://www.womanizer.com/eu/privacy-policy#gi-gp) section under (8.1.).

**14\. Social Media Websites**

We use the following social media operators:

* Facebook
* LinkedIn
* Twitter
* Instagram
* Pinterest
* Snapchat
* Youtube
* XING

The operators of the social media platforms (e.g. Facebook) are involved in the operation of the websites just listed. They are also responsible (controllers) within the meaning of data protection law. We can hardly influence the data processing carried out by the platform operators and are dependent on the information the respective providers give us. To the extent we can exert influence and have a part in determining data processing, we aim to ensure that the operator of the social media platform treats the data in a manner appropriate to data protection.

#### **15\. Data processed by us**

The data you disclose using our social media pages, such as comments, videos, pictures, likes, public news, etc. are published by the social media platform. We only reserve the right to comment on or delete content if this is necessary. In some cases, we share your content on our site and communicate with you through the social media platform. We use the social media platforms for advertising purposes. The statistics made available to us by the provider of the social media platform can only be influenced to a limited extent and cannot be switched off. The legal basis is our legitimate interest in carrying out the aforementioned processes (Art. 6 para. 1 f) GDPR).

If you wish to object to a specific data processing on which we have an influence, please contact the address given in [imprint](https://wowtech.com/privacy-policy/).

#### **Data processed by the operators of social media platforms**

Social media platform operators use web tracking methods. Web tracking can be performed regardless of whether you are logged in or registered with the social media platform. As already mentioned, we can hardly influence the web tracking methods of the social media platform and for example cannot switch it off. It cannot be excluded that the provider of the social media platform may use data, for example to evaluate habits, personal relationships, preferences, etc. In this area we have no influence on the processing of data by the platform operator.

Further information on data processing by the provider of the social media platform and further possibilities for objection can be found in the data protection declaration of the providers:

Twitter: [https://twitter.com/de/privacy](https://twitter.com/de/privacy)

Facebook: [https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)

YouTube: [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=de](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=de)

LinkedIn: [https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy?trk=hb\_ft\_priv](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy?trk=hb_ft_priv)

Instagram: [https://help.instagram.com/155833707900388](https://help.instagram.com/155833707900388)

Pinterest: [https://policy.pinterest.com/de/privacy-policy](https://policy.pinterest.com/de/privacy-policy)

Snapchat: [https://www.snap.com/de-DE/privacy/privacy-policy](https://www.snap.com/de-DE/privacy/privacy-policy)

XING: [https://privacy.xing.com/de/datenschutzerklaerung](https://privacy.xing.com/de/datenschutzerklaerung)

#### **15\. Disclosure of Data to Third Parties**

We work with service providers who assist us in providing our services on this website. These service providers are named in the relevant areas within this Data Protection policy and process data solely on behalf of and under the control of WOW and only for the purposes described in this Data Protection Policy.

#### **16\. Retention of Data**

Personal data is stored for as long as is necessary for the above-mentioned purposes. The data will be deleted at the latest after termination of the contractual relationship and after expiry of the statutory retention periods of civil, commercial and tax law.

Data that is collected while surfing on our website (see section 1) and that can legally be considered personal data (e.g. the complete IP address) is stored for a period of 14 days, unless an unusual incident requires a longer storage period (e.g. after a hacker attack).

If we process data on the basis of legitimate interests (Art. 6 para. 1 f) GDPR), these will be stored until you object to the processing or until your legitimate interests prevail.

### **Your Rights / Contact Information**

#### **General Rights**

You can request access to the personal data stored about you and have the right to receive the data you provided in a common and machine-readable format. In addition, you may, in justified cases, request the deletion, correction or limitation of the processing of your data. If you have given us your consent, you can revoke it at any time with effect for the future. If your personal data are transferred to a country outside the EU that does not offer adequate protection, you can request a copy of the contract that ensures adequate protection of personal data. You also have a general right to complain to a supervisory authority about our data processing.

#### **Opt-out**

If we use your personal data on the basis of our legitimate interests, you may **object** to the processing and use of your data. In this case, we will no longer use your data unless our interests prevail. You can object to the use of your data for direct marketing purposes at any time without further consideration.

#### **Contact Information**

In order to exercise the aforementioned rights, please contact us directly in writing or via e-mail or contact our Data Protection Officer under datenschutz Nord GmbH, Kurfürstendamm 212, 10719 Berlin, Germany, [datenschutz@wowtech.com](mailto:datenschutz@wowtech.com).

Still need help or have suggestions, or feedback?

Help

Legal

* Cookie Settings

Company

Contact

Secure Payment With:

* 

COPYRIGHT © 2024 WOW TECH EUROPE GMBH ALL RIGHTS RESERVED
